SIDDHANT MOHAPATRA () Featured

Software Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Technical Analysis, Production Support, Process Improvement, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, JavaScript, Java, Spring Boot, SQL, React



Current Designation: Software Developer, Member Technical Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 2 Month(s)

Notice Period: 1 Month Current Company: Automatic Data Processing Pvt. Ltd (ADP)

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad Highest Degree: Other [Other]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Technical Analysis, Production Support, Process Improvement, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Java Script, Java, Spring Boot, SQL, React

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

Having 3.2 yrs. experience in full stack development.

Hands-on experience on JavaScript, React, Java, Spring Boot, web services (REST API), SQL, Hibernate.

Also worked on production support analysis and solving the production defects.

Knowledge of Visual Studio, STS (Spring Tool Suite), Jira, Rally for the development of projects.

Good Communication skills, ability to work as part of an integrated team as well as independently.

Ability to learn new tools and language quickly

Work Experience

Automatic Data Processing Pvt. Ltd (ADP) as Software Developer, Member Technical Jul 2017 to Till Date

Automatic Data Processing Pvt. Ltd (ADP) as Software Developer Jul 2017 to Jul 2017

- 1. Project: Request Carryover (2019-2020) Role: Software Developer Technologies: JavaScript, React and Redux Location: Hyderabad Description: Request Carryover is time off that was earned but not yet used by an employee during the period for which it was earned. The option to use carryover must be set up in the Time Off Policy. If the carryover is Automatic, the carryover amount will automatically be carried over according to the setup for the time off policy and it can also be requested manually. If the carryover is Manual, the request for carryover must be made by the employee, manager, or practitioner on behalf of the employee.
- 2. Project: Content Rights (2019) Role: Software Developer Technologies: JavaScript, React and Redux Location: Hyderabad Description: Practitioners set up viewing or editing rights for employees and managers to view or edit specific Policy Name/Content associated with time off policies.
- 3. Project: Payroll Register Report (2018-2019) Role: Software Developer Technologies: Java, Spring Boot, Oracle, Kafka, REST API Location Pune Description: A payroll register is a record of all pay details for employees during a specific pay period. The payroll register lists information about each employee for things such as gross pay, net pay, and deductions and so on. The register also lists the totals for all employees combined during the period. At the end of the payroll register, after all employee information is listed, there is a totals section. This is where all the employee information is combined.

4. Project: Retro Pay (2017-2018) Role: Software Developer Technologies: JavaScript, React and Redux, Java, Spring Boot, Oracle Location: Pune Description: Retro Pay lets you pay an employee for a retroactive rate change. This is useful when there is a late change to an employee's pay rate, or if your company receives a court or union order to change an employee's base pay as of a past date. If a practitioner changes an employee's pay rate on the Regular Pay page and the effective date occurs in a prior pay period, then the Retro Pay Requests tab displays rate change details for the employee. Then you select a record to calculate and it will include it in current payroll.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Institute of Technical Education and Research, Bhuvaneshwar in 2017

PG: Other (Other) in 0

IT Skills

| Skill Name | Version Last Used Experience |
|-------------------------|------------------------------|
| Java, JavaScript, React | |
| SQL/Oracle | |
| Hibernate | |
| spring boot | |
| web service (rest api) | |

Languages Known

| Language | Proficiency | Read | Write | Speak |
|----------|-------------|------|-------|-------|
| English | | | | |
| Hindi | | | | |
| Odia | | | | |

Affirmative Action

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

Category: General

Employment Status: Full time

Work Authorization